<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="80">
  <author>Peppie84</author>
  <version>0.0.2.1</version>
  <title>
    <en>Bees Revamp</en>
    <de>Bees Revamp</de>
  </title>
  <description>
    <en><![CDATA[
  With this mod, the bees in Farming Simulator 22 become more realistic and a bit more complex but also more productive.

  All values ​​and changes are scientifically proven and/or perhaps slightly adjusted so that they do not completely kill the fun of the game. The focus will always be on having fun.

  Most questions can be answered by the in-game help of this mod.

  - Two states of a colony (young colony and economic colony)
  - Only the economic colony produces honey
  - Bees collect nectar
  - Bees only collect when the weather is good
  - Nectar is converted into honey
  - Bees eat nectar
  - Range of the beehives has been increased
  - Pollination performance improved
  - Beehive has a variable number of bees
  - Swarming season is between Mar-Jul
  - Prices of the beehives have been adjusted
  - Honey sales price has been adjusted
  - Precision farming compatible

  Currently no multiplayer support.

  For more information, help, and reporting issues please visit <a href='https://github.com/Peppie84/FS22_BeesRevamp'>GitHub</a>.
]]></en>
    <de><![CDATA[
Mit dieser Mod werden die Bienen im Landwirtschafts-Simulator 22 realistischer und auch etwas komplexer aber dafür auch ertragreicher.

Alle Werte und Änderungen sind wissenschaftlich belegt und oder vielleicht etwas angepasst, damit sie nicht ein kompletter Spielspaß-Killer werden. Im Vordergrund wird immer der Spielspaß stehen.

Bitte schau Dir die Ingame-Hilfe zu dieser Mod an. Sie kann die meisten Fragen beantworten.

- Zwei Zustände eines Volkes (Jungvolk und Wirtschaftsvolk)
- Nur das Wirtschaftsvolk bringt Honig
- Bienen sammeln Nektar
- Bienen sammeln nur bei schönem Wetter
- Nektar wird in Honig umgewandelt
- Bienen fressen Nektar
- Reichweite der Bienenstöcke wurde erhöht
- Besteubungsleistung verbessert
- Bienenstock hat eine variable Anzahl an Bienen
- Zwischen Mär-Jul ist Schwarmzeit
- Preise der Bienenstöcke wurden angepasst
- Honigverkaufspreis wurde angepasst
- Precision Farming kompatibel

Aktuell kein Multiplayer support.

Weitere Informationen, Hilfe und Probleme melden findest Du unter <a href='https://github.com/Peppie84/FS22_BeesRevamp'>GitHub</a>.
]]></de>
  </description>
  <dependencies>
    <dependency>FS22_beeHivesWood</dependency>
    <dependency>FS22_SmallBeehives01</dependency>
  </dependencies>
  <iconFilename>icon_BeesRevamp.dds</iconFilename>
  <multiplayer supported="false" />
  <extraSourceFiles>
    <sourceFile filename="src/main.lua" />
  </extraSourceFiles>
  <l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation" />
</modDesc>
