<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="80">
  <author>Peppie84</author>
  <version>1.1.0.1</version>
  <title>
    <en>Bees Revamp</en>
  </title>
  <description>
    <en><![CDATA[
With this mod, bees in Farming Simulator 22 become more realistic and a bit more complex but also more productive.

All values and changes are scientifically proven and/or perhaps slightly adjusted so that they do not completely kill the fun of the game. The focus will always be on having fun.

Most questions can be answered by the in-game help of this mod.

- Two states of a colony (young colony and economic colony)
- Only the economic colony produces honey
- Bees collect nectar
- Bees only collect when the weather is good
- Nectar is converted into honey
- Bees eat nectar
- Range of the beehives has been increased
- Pollination performance improved
- Beehive has a variable number of bees
- Swarming season is between Mar-Jul
- Prices of the beehives have been adjusted
- Honey sales price has been adjusted
- Precision farming compatible
- TerraLife compatible

Yield bonus for: Canola, Sunflower, Alfalfa, Clover, Buckwheat, Phacelia, Silphie, Mustard and Clover gras

Additional supported bee hives:
- Pack Of Beehives by BarT
- Wooden Hive For Bees by Fr€d Fra-Cassés
- Beehives Pack by Zoli708
- Beehouse by MefiuFs
- Bee Hive Trailer by Maca
- Beehive With 3 Large Frames by doodoo
- Beehouse by Ls_Dezign

Changelog v1.1.0.1
- Fixed Number to string conversion for formatting the nectar info for en and it language

Changelog v1.1.0.0
- Added multiplayer functionality
- Reduced load while playing with precision farming and calculating the field info
- Added translation for IT
- Added support for more bee hive mods
- Fixed a bug for conversion from TerraLife weeks in stock month for the last week in Feb

For more information, help, and reporting issues please visit <a href='https://github.com/Peppie84/FS22_BeesRevamp'>GitHub</a>.
]]></en>
    <de><![CDATA[
Mit dieser Mod werden die Bienen im Landwirtschafts-Simulator 22 realistischer und auch etwas komplexer aber dafür auch ertragreicher.

Alle Werte und Änderungen sind wissenschaftlich belegt und oder vielleicht etwas angepasst, damit sie nicht ein kompletter Spielspaß-Killer werden. Im Vordergrund wird immer der Spielspaß stehen.

Bitte schau Dir die Ingame-Hilfe zu dieser Mod an. Sie kann die meisten Fragen beantworten.

- Zwei Zustände eines Volkes (Jungvolk und Wirtschaftsvolk)
- Nur das Wirtschaftsvolk bringt Honig
- Bienen sammeln Nektar
- Bienen sammeln nur bei schönem Wetter
- Nektar wird in Honig umgewandelt
- Bienen fressen Nektar
- Reichweite der Bienenstöcke wurde erhöht
- Besteubungsleistung verbessert
- Bienenstock hat eine variable Anzahl an Bienen
- Zwischen Mär-Jul ist Schwarmzeit
- Preise der Bienenstöcke wurden angepasst
- Honigverkaufspreis wurde angepasst
- Precision Farming kompatibel
- TerraLife kompatibel

Ertragsbonus für: Raps, Sonnenblume, Luzerne, Klee, Buchweizen, Phacelia, Silphie, Senf und Kleegras

Zusätzlich unterstützte Bienenstöcke:
- Bienenstöcke von BarT
- Hölzerner Bienenstock Für Bienen von Fr€d Fra-Cassés
- Bienenstock-Paket von Zoli708
- Bienenhaus von MefiuFs
- Bienenanhänger von Maca
- Bienenstock Mit 3 Grossen Zargen von doodoo
- Bienenhaus von Ls_Dezign

Changelog v1.1.0.1
- Konvertierung von Zahlen in Zeichenfolgen zum formatieren der Nectar-Informationen für die Sprachen EN und IT, behoben

Changelog v1.1.0.0
- Multiplayer funktionalität hinzugefügt
- Veringert die Rechenlast zur Berechnung der Feldinfo mit PrecisionFarmin
- Übersetzung für IT hinzugefügt
- Es werden weitere Bienenmods unterstützt
- Fehler bei der Umrechnung von TerraLife Wochen in Stock Monat behoben, der in der letzten Feb Woche geworfen wurde

Weitere Informationen, Hilfe und Probleme melden findest Du unter <a href='https://github.com/Peppie84/FS22_BeesRevamp'>GitHub</a>.
]]></de>
    <it><![CDATA[
Con questa mod, le api in Farming Simulator 22 diventano più realistiche e un po' più complesse ma anche più produttive.

Tutti i valori e le modifiche sono scientificamente provati e/o forse leggermente regolati in modo che non uccidano completamente il divertimento del gioco. L'obiettivo sarà sempre il divertimento.

La maggior parte delle domande può essere risolta dall'aiuto in-game di questa mod.

- Due stati di una colonia (colonia giovane e colonia economica)
- Solo la colonia economica produce miele
- Le api raccolgono nettare
- Le api raccolgono solo quando il tempo è buono
- Il nettare viene convertito in miele
- Le api mangiano nettare
- La portata degli alveari è stata aumentata
- Prestazioni di impollinazione migliorate
- L'alveare ha un numero variabile di api
- La stagione dello sciame è tra Mar-Lug
- I prezzi degli alveari sono stati regolati
- Il prezzo di vendita del miele è stato regolato
- Compatibile con precision farming
- Compatibile con TerraLife

Bonus di resa per: Colza, Girasole, Erba Medica, Trifoglio, Grano Saraceno, Facelia, Silphie, Senape e Erba di Trifoglio

Alveari aggiuntivi supportati:
- Pacchetto di Alveari di BarT
- Alveare di Legno per Api di Fr€d Fra-Cassés
- Pacchetto alveari di Zoli708
- Apicoltura di MefiuFs
- Rimorchio per alveari di Maca
- Arnia con 3 telaini grandi di doodoo
- Apicoltura di Ls_Dezign

Changelog v1.1.0.1
- Conversione fissa da numero a stringa per formattare le informazioni di Nectar per le lingue EN e IT

Changelog v1.1.0.0
- Aggiunta della funzionalità multigiocatore
- Riduzione del carico durante il gioco dell'agricoltura di precisione e il calcolo delle informazioni sul campo
- Aggiunta traduzione per IT
- Aggiunto il supporto per altri modelli di alveare
- Corretto un bug per la conversione da TerraLife delle settimane del mese di magazzino per l'ultima settimana di febbraio.

Per ulteriori informazioni, aiuto e segnalazione di problemi, visita <a href='https://github.com/Peppie84/FS22_BeesRevamp'>GitHub</a>.
]]></it>
  </description>
  <iconFilename>icon_BeesRevamp.dds</iconFilename>
  <multiplayer supported="true" />
  <extraSourceFiles>
    <sourceFile filename="src/main.lua" />
  </extraSourceFiles>
  <l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation" />
</modDesc>